Hi.
Today, I'm having a barbecue at my parents' house.
I invited a third term student to my parents' house for a barbecue.
Yay!
Yay! It's delicious!
They've been asking me to come over to my parents' house for a few years.
have been asking me to go to my parents' house for a few years.
I haven't had a chance to make it happen so I thought it would be fun to make a YouTube video or something.
I suggested that it would be fun to make a YouTube video or something.
And it was so easy to do.
And everyone was so excited about it.
Everyone's in the mood for it.
I'd like to try it.
I'll do it.
Yay!
I'm going to go shopping now and head to my parents' house.
Yes, ma'am.
Bon appétit.
Cheers.
What's this?
I don't know.
Dad?
You're crying.
Okay.
It's very youthful.
You're so cute.
What do you want to eat? What do you want to cook?
Zucchini!
Meat! Meat!
Steak 20% off.
You want a big one?
Don't you want it?
Sure, let's grill it.
Super thick.
Let's grill up some seafood, like shrimp.
I don't know. Tataki.
You don't eat tataki at American Express.
We have popcorn.
That's good.
I want some watermelon.
Watermelon.
Watermelon!
Yay!
It's raining so hard!
Thank you for your time.
I'll prepare the ingredients.
I bought onions, zucchini, green peppers, shrimp, corn, and yams
I have no choice but to buy green peppers because I don't have enough green peppers.
I like them.
Can I have half already?
I'm scared.
Oh, I'm scared
The way you cut it.
I can't look at it anymore.
It's so thin. It's an onion.
No green plums.
Maybe it stopped raining. Really?
That's what I'm talking about. That's what I'm talking about, Mommy.
It's done!
Mintan!
I'm so happy!
You can do it in the garage?
You can do it in the garage.
That's so cool!
That's great.
Then you can sit here and stuff.
It's cool.
Is this the Lenkantu chair?
Len-Chiu's chair.
Can I put it like this?
Lenka's mom bought this after seeing my chow mein. Dashi Shoyu and Rockske's salt.
Lenka's mom is easily influenced.
Let's make a fire. Let's start with the charcoal.
How do we line it up? Is there any way to make it stronger? Wait, it's an assembly line, right?
Don't pack it in too tight. Leave some space. Leave some space.
In the middle.
Fire. Open the airway. What? That's what it says.
Is that it?
Let's go a little further, shall we? Oh, that's good, right?
It's good, right? I'm going to use a gas burner with this.
But, you know, we're going to need some kind of a fuel source.
Like this?
Like an igniter.
It says "easy" on it.
It says "Easy" on it.
It looks like that.
You know, like the kind you get at your grandma's house.
It's like a piece of bonito.
What's that?
You're supposed to put the burning ones under the coals.
That's right.
So why don't you just put the coals on top? A little more.
Oh, In-chan! Yin-chan!
That's great! It's burning so hot!
Hey, hey, hey.
I think we're in fourth place.
Now that's how I respect blue hair!
Now I adore blue hairs!
Blue hair is precious
I was just making fun of the fact that you have blue hair.
No, I know.
I know you have blue hair.
I'm totally fine.
It's summer.
My relatives' grandparents have been doing this all their lives.
They'll be drinking like this for the rest of their lives.
It's nice, isn't it?
We should have bought some snacks.
The kids play here.
Good night.
What do you think? The sides are so beautiful.
Minami Umezawa, the nice girl who starts fires.
Minami Umezawa. Stop it.
Turn around.
Oh, wink.
Pow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Funny face, funny face.
How do you guys wink when you're in Gullu? Do you do it?
I do.
You don't?
I can't do it. Try it. Try it.
Daddy run.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah.
rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, that's good.
Let's try it again.
You got the other one?
I'm doing the blue one.
But it must be hard being a dad.
They do all this for you, don't they?
But, you know, it's the only thing I can do.
Come on.
Stop it.
What's this?
I don't know.
Hey, Dad.
It's burning.
Help me build a fire.
It's not catching.
Hi, Dad.
You put too much charcoal in the fire.
I'm hungry.
What?
Did I put in too much?
Can't we just light a few more, then put them on top of each other?
Can't we just spread them out and go home?
I mean...
I got a father-son co-starring.
That's how you use it.
Hey...
I thought I'd put it in here.
And then say, "This one's different.
What's this?
And then you say, "No, thanks.
Okay. You want to make a toast?
Yeah, let's have one toast.
Let's let the parents build the fire.
Excuse me, sir.
Thank you very much.
Cheers.
To summer.
Here's to midsummer.
Wide, wide
Delicious
Delicious!
Now, you see this screen, right?
Look at it again. It's really big.
From the front here, to the back here, aren't they all lenghans?
That's the one you're looking at, right?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What? Oh, no!
It's turning this way! It's spinning this way!
Sorry, sorry, it's me.
It's not spinning.
It's this way. It's this way.
I'll give you one more toast.
To summer!
Say it!
You were moving like crazy.
I was getting pretty good at it.
I was making all these little jokes. I'm too new at this.
Can you please use a little voice with a face icon?
You're good.
I finally got a camera.
I finally got a camera!
It's just like home. It's like home.
This is my parents' house!
This way! Yuu's parents' house!
It's so slow!
I made it on my own.
It's been a year!
It's not over yet!
It's not over yet.
But I know... when summer's over, it's over.
Don't you think summer's coming?
I know, I know.
It seems like we have a long summer, but it's so short because we're talking.
It's like we're just trying to get to the end of the year.
The way the group works.
And then it's New Year's Eve.
And then it's New Year's Eve?
This is the kind of talk you have over dinner.
There's nothing more to do.
Once, once...
Spread it out. I'll tell you the same story again.
But I don't think it will be used. It's almost never used.
What can we do for the kids?
They're not children, actually.
They are adults.
Thank you very much.
That's it. That's it.
That's great.
Oh, here it comes!
It's saying "sizzle.
No, it's coming.
This is it.
It smells so good.
Wow!
It's so fiery, I can't turn it over.
Thank you, Mom and Dad.
Turn it over.
Surprisingly good!
It's absolutely delicious.
Oh, my God.
Looks so good!
Yes, trash.
It's hot! It's so hot!
It's like barbecue.
I love the heat.
Bon appétit!
I only brought chopsticks.
Thanks.
Haa!
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Whoa! Whoa! Wow!
Oh, my God, Pariah.
Is it good?
Yeah!
Hot!
The fire's in great position.
Isn't it so good?
The seasoning is so good!
It's delicious!
It's so cool.
Can you cut it with your teeth?
No, I don't think so.
It's good, right?
It's so good.
It's delicious.
I have some rice if anyone wants some.
Is that possible?
You're the first one to eat it.
Oh, my gosh...
It's a line-of-sight camera.
Plum eye camera.
Is it really good?
Yeah, it's really good.
Lili's face is right there.
Oh, my God, Tan, look.
Oh, my God!
It's so hot!
Jingu.
I made a mistake.
Is it hotter than this?
Hot, hot
Jingu now
Only here, people are early Jingu now
Toshiwave at Jingu
Though the number of burnt items is still a little small!
Bon appétit!
The endless ragpicking of boropassi
You mean you were thankful to your relatives
That's about it.
Thank you, mother.
Thank you.
It's a cucumber.
Here.
Does beef tongue have any flavor?
No.
No beef tongue, no sauce.
I love salt.
It's really good.
This is amazing.
I put it on a long time ago.
It's bad.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Just a little bit on the side.
I want some too.
Bon appétit!
No problem.
Thank you.
Is it good?
How is it?
Bon appétit.
Beef tongue.
Maybe too good.
It's good.
Oh, my God!
The salt is so good!
It's so good just as it is!
Try making onigiri with it.
It's so good!
You should come over and make some rice balls.
Sure.
You're coming to cook?
Come over to my place.
I'd rather go to college.
I'm calling the chef.
Come to my place.
Momo ladry.
He's a god, isn't he?
Elibata is a god!
Please give me an eribata insert!
Open
Insert of Eribata
Sparkling effect, please!
eringi
I'd like to put a little more lid on it.
Eringi.
What did you say?
Elingi. - Elingi.
Elingi! Elingi!
eringi
Elingi.
Let's hide them.
It's so colorful.
It's kind of like a barbecue, isn't it?
It's like this.
Okay, so, let's do it before the barbecue.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. What was that?
Wait, we're in a sea of salt.
Oh, my God.
But it's not a sea of salt, it's a pile of salt.
I'm sad to say that I'm not a magician...
I, Renkan family dog, cat, and octopus, can introduce you.
There's all of them, and they're amazing.
I'm good friends with my mom at home.
They call you Aya?
Aya!
You've called me Aya a few times already.
We even stopped at the house before it was rebuilt.
Is that so?
That feels good.
Ya-ya-ya!
Long, long, long.
I'm ready!
I'm not thinking anything funny.
I'm really too private!
I'm going to get a huge steak!
I'll take this one.
Juwan!
It won't work.
What's in it?
Oh, my God!
I'll find a place to put it.
Thank you very much.
Wait a minute.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Shoshu-age on the verge of eating
Yay, yay, yay.
Excuse me.
Here we go!
Ready?
Wow.
Amazing.
Same.
Maru-burnt
It's not the same.
Looks soft! So soft!
Ta-da!
Aaah!
Look! Midea manera!
It's good! It's so good! There's so much steam!
It looks good!
This one's bigger.
Bon appétit!
Piece of steak
So tender! It's so tender.
Steak, then.
Cheers!
A little more salt and pepper
With 6 skewers of oshiketo.
Six skewers for now!
Yum! It's so good!
So good!
Here it comes.
Oh, my God, it smells like caramel.
Here comes the peabar.
Peabar type.
Zing, zing, zing.
Oh, my God.
I'll make you marshmallows now.
Go, go, go.
Is it hot?
Hot.
Where are you going?
Ta-ran.
I can't take a hit.
It's always been that way.
Don't you think I work a lot?
Don't you think I sit around all the time at Nogichu and stuff?
I think so.
I think you sit on your feet.
I can't imagine what it must have been like in the old days.
Now I'd like to do a fruit punch.
I'll do it!
And my mom bought fireworks!
Yay!
I'm going to set off the fireworks later!
Okay, first we're going to play Fruit Punch.
You want some?
Here we go. Yeah.
Soy milk.
Oh!
Wow!
Room temperature cider.
Well, well, well.
It's okay, right?
Let's eat.
Shwah, shwah, shwah, shwah.
Thank you.
It's so yellow.
Bon appétit.
Let's have some pineapple.
Is it good? Not at all. Sols is cold.
Wow! Thank you!
Lenka's mom peeled it for us. Thank you.
Ta-da! Lenka's mom made it.
Cake! Thank you for the cake. It's so cute.
It's a low-calorie cheesecake.
It's delicious. It's so delicious.
It's so good. It's so good. It's so good? It's so good. It's so good. It's so good?
It's very healthy. - Hey, this is definitely a girl's favorite.
Let's sell them! Let's sell them! On Nogizaka's website!
We don't have many handheld fireworks in Tokyo. We really don't.
We can't really do that.
The winner says something to the loser... and the loser says something to the winner... and the winner says something to the loser.
Okay, purple. Bichon from Nogizaka.
You've got to be kidding me. Get away, get away!
Here it comes!
Yay!
Yay! - Yay! It's so adolescent!
It's so adolescent!
I don't have time for this.
Instead of enjoying the moment, it's a picture!
It's over before it opens!
Oh, no!
It's gonna be over before I can open it.
Shut up.
Oh, my God, it's so loud! Oh, my God, it's so loud!
Can I get a long shot, please?
Longy?
That's really nice.
You changed the color.
It changes color so much.
Oh, my God.
Emo.
Heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart heart
It's over.
Oh, it changed color... again.
Shapes?
Me too, I changed my color.
It's so long.
Orabicinite.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, just in time.
It's a generational shift.
Generation change.
Oh, that's nice...
I wonder how many more times I can enjoy this youth
The color's changed.
I'm dying of smoke
Yes, I'm dying of smoke
It's all going to the billiards.
It's a showdown.
You know, we all have to wear these at the same time.
That's right.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Good morning.
We're almost there.
They're here.
They're here, they're here, they're here.
It's windy.
Don't go away!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's the end of the summer... we had a great time... thanks for today... have a great summer... and we'll be waiting for you...
Lili, you're so beautiful, you're so beautiful, it's picture time, picture time, picture time.
It's photo time... photo time... photo time...
I wish I could see and photograph them.
I'm still here.
I'm still here. This one's still alive.
It's like a thousand and one, isn't it?
Plum blossoms!
Plum!
Plum blossoms for the win!
Yay!
Buy me an ice cream.
I didn't buy him ice cream!
So today I invited the 3rd term students to my parents' house for a barbecue to feel the summer!
Yay!
It was a lot of fun!
We did so many summer things!
All the moms and dads were there!
My mom and dad were on the wall, too!
I hope you all had a great summer!
Let's do it again!
I want to do it again!
If there's a second one, we'll do it.
I'll do it.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
Have a great summer!
Happy Summertime!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe!
I'll turn it off.
It's okay.
Say bye-bye, everybody.
Bye-bye.